{
    "subject": "resource/Mario_Calire",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Mario Calire was born in United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9831994771957397,
            "question": "Is Mario Calire's birthplace in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.88043612241745,
            "question": "Where was Mario Calire born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.835396409034729,
            "question": "What year was Mario Calire born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6414876580238342,
            "question": "What nationality is Mario Calire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5203621983528137,
            "question": "What country is Mario Calire from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48266807198524475,
            "question": "What is Mario Calire known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34994545578956604,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Mario Calire's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2833574116230011,
            "question": "Where might Mario Calire live now?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.270560622215271,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Mario Calire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26258039474487305,
            "question": "Do you know anything else about Mario Calire?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mario Calire was born in United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9225_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Mario Calire?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9225_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might Mario Calire live now?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9225_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Mario Calire's family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9225_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9225_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9225_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9225_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9225_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9225_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9225_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9225_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9225_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9225_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9225_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information that Mario Calire was born on June 25, 1974, in Buffalo, New York, USA. This confirms that Mario Calire was indeed born in the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}